You've probably seen the impossible happen, or at least thought you have.
你可能见过不可能发生的事情，或者至少以为你见过。
When a magician makes a card disappear, or throws a ball into the air, only for it to vanish, it seems that they are using amazing powers.
当魔术师让一张牌消失，或者把一个球抛向空中却消失了，看起来他们似乎在使用不可思议的力量。
But the magic isn't happening on stage.
但魔术并不是在舞台上发生的。
It's actually all inside your brain.
实际上，它全部发生在你的大脑里。
These illusions work because of essential processes that happen in our brains.
这些错觉之所以奏效，是因为发生在我们大脑中的基本过程。
Our senses provide an enormous amount of information about our surroundings.
我们的感官提供了大量关于周围环境的信息。
Our brains have evolved ways of prioritising what's important.
我们的大脑已经进化出对重要信息进行优先处理的方式。
We tend to notice the things that are most significant and remember those which have most meaning for us.
我们倾向于注意最重要的事情，并记住那些对我们最有意义的事情。
What we perceive that we see or remember that we saw is actually a mental image.
我们感知到看到的或记得看到的东西，实际上是一种精神意向。
These mental processes are exploited by illusionists to trick us into perceiving things in a particular way.
这些心理过程被魔术师利用来欺骗我们，让我们以特定的方式感知事物。
In one famous trick, a ball is thrown into the air twice and caught and then vanishes into thin air on the third throw.
在一个著名的戏法中，一个球被抛向空中两次并接住，然后在第三次抛出时消失得无影无踪。
This third throw is actually just a hand movement.
这第三次抛出实际上只是一个手部动作。
Our brains predict that the ball will leave the magician's hand so we think we see it.
我们的大脑预测球会离开魔术师的手，所以我们以为我们看到了它。
The same process makes a dog run for a stick when we pretend to throw it.
当我们假装扔棍子时，同样的过程使得狗会跑去追棍子。
During a magic show, we are often manipulated to think that we have a freer choice than we actually do.
在魔术表演中，我们常常被操控，以为自己拥有比实际更自由的选择。
Magician-turned-psychologist Gustav Kuhn highlights how a performer's gaze can direct our attention towards some things and divert it away from others.
魔术师出身的心理学家古斯塔夫·库恩强调了表演者的目光如何将我们的注意力引向某些事物，并使其偏离其他事物。
Even babies naturally tend to follow where someone is looking.
即使是婴儿也天生倾向于跟随别人注视的方向。
Kuhn has become a researcher using the techniques behind different magic tricks to see what we can learn about how the brain works.
库恩已经成为一名研究人员，利用不同魔术背后的技术来探究我们可以从中学到什么关于大脑运作的知识。
He's even teamed up with a toy manufacturer to produce magic sets that explain our mental processes.
他甚至与一家玩具制造商合作，生产解释我们心理过程的魔术套装。
Understanding these could be important because while magicians use these deceptions to entertain us, others use similar approaches to mislead us or spread disinformation.
理解这些可能很重要，因为虽然魔术师用这些骗术来娱乐我们，但其他人却用类似的方法来误导我们或传播虚假信息。